<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@avery.wade.kelley</id>
  <title>@avery.wade.kelley | TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-09-18T17:52:09+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://tiktokrss.uselesslesbians.gay/rss/avery.wade.kelley.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://tiktokrss.uselesslesbians.gay/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>Latest TikToks from @avery.wade.kelley</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@avery.wade.kelley/video/7275845287946554666</id>
    <title>Lol... No, but for real. #fyp </title>
    <updated>2023-09-06T22:35:53+00:00</updated>
    <content>Lol... No, but for real. #fyp </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@avery.wade.kelley/video/7275845287946554666" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-06T22:35:53+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@avery.wade.kelley/video/7276173505580911914</id>
    <title>Life lessons. ALWAYS do your research for stylists, tattoo artists, micro-blading technicians, surgons, anyone that does a permanent or semi-permanent modification on your body. I ended up being really mean to this person because I was so upset, but at th</title>
    <updated>2023-09-07T19:49:34+00:00</updated>
    <content>Life lessons. ALWAYS do your research for stylists, tattoo artists, micro-blading technicians, surgons, anyone that does a permanent or semi-permanent modification on your body. I ended up being really mean to this person because I was so upset, but at the end of the day, it was my fault for allowing it to happen and not fully communicating and doing my research, and they didn't deserve the anger I dished out on them.  Be careful, ask for what you want, and don't settle. Even if it takes you years to find the right artist, I promise it's worth it.  Have patience.  - Not Chester #fyp </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@avery.wade.kelley/video/7276173505580911914" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-07T19:49:34+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@avery.wade.kelley/video/7276510545795124523</id>
    <title>In less than a month, I leave my home state, fleeing because of the rediculous laws put in place for trans people.  The last time I moved out of Florida, I went to WA in 2012 and lived there for two years. I was young and reckless, experiencing beautiful </title>
    <updated>2023-09-08T17:37:25+00:00</updated>
    <content>In less than a month, I leave my home state, fleeing because of the rediculous laws put in place for trans people.  The last time I moved out of Florida, I went to WA in 2012 and lived there for two years. I was young and reckless, experiencing beautiful and ugly things, and fell straight on my ass. Homeless, jobless, no car, no hope. My mom flew me back home where I came into myself through a plethora of difficult life lessons.  This is scary for me, but I'm trying to me excited about it. Everything I've known, all my memories, my security in seeing the Spanish Moss over the brick roads of downtown, the booming thunderstorms... I will miss the Swamp dearly.  But I'm excited to ascend into the clouds, a mile high in the sky, on a mountain...  Maybe I'll be able to touch the stars, and that's exciting... #fyp #trans </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@avery.wade.kelley/video/7276510545795124523" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-08T17:37:25+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@avery.wade.kelley/video/7276854116523969838</id>
    <title>Seriously, it's a problem. Leave us alone, we're not doing absolutely anything to you OR your children but offering education and acceptance. #fyp #trans </title>
    <updated>2023-09-09T15:50:37+00:00</updated>
    <content>Seriously, it's a problem. Leave us alone, we're not doing absolutely anything to you OR your children but offering education and acceptance. #fyp #trans </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@avery.wade.kelley/video/7276854116523969838" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-09T15:50:37+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@avery.wade.kelley/video/7278001199327137070</id>
    <title>Just another Life Lesson. Things will change eventually. It's a part of life. Whether you've lost someone, or have chosen a new career path, or even met someone new; It's a change. So, ride with it. Feel the feelings that come with it. And just experience</title>
    <updated>2023-09-12T18:02:08+00:00</updated>
    <content>Just another Life Lesson. Things will change eventually. It's a part of life. Whether you've lost someone, or have chosen a new career path, or even met someone new; It's a change. So, ride with it. Feel the feelings that come with it. And just experience. Just be. #fyp #trans </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@avery.wade.kelley/video/7278001199327137070" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-12T18:02:08+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@avery.wade.kelley/video/7278051085527371050</id>
    <title>#duet with @ErinInTheMorning #Trans </title>
    <updated>2023-09-12T21:15:32+00:00</updated>
    <content>#duet with @ErinInTheMorning #Trans </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@avery.wade.kelley/video/7278051085527371050" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-12T21:15:32+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@avery.wade.kelley/video/7278730463450041646</id>
    <title>Such a simple concept that so many grasp, and others don't. I struggle with feeding myself every single day, and doing the things I need to do such as cleaning the house or planning doctors visits. If you take care of plants, try taking care of yourself w</title>
    <updated>2023-09-14T17:11:50+00:00</updated>
    <content>Such a simple concept that so many grasp, and others don't. I struggle with feeding myself every single day, and doing the things I need to do such as cleaning the house or planning doctors visits. If you take care of plants, try taking care of yourself while you're doing the same for them. Got a dog? Prepare both of your meals at the same time. We deserve to be cared for by ourselves. You're worth that, I promise. #fyp #mentalhealth #trans </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@avery.wade.kelley/video/7278730463450041646" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-14T17:11:50+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@avery.wade.kelley/video/7279150360457907502</id>
    <title>Sober from alcohol for almost 3 years, and I feel the difference. I was slowly killing myself with it, and when I stopped, it took a while for everything to stop hurting too. But, it's getting better. The main focus is today, and that's all we can do. Lov</title>
    <updated>2023-09-15T20:21:16+00:00</updated>
    <content>Sober from alcohol for almost 3 years, and I feel the difference. I was slowly killing myself with it, and when I stopped, it took a while for everything to stop hurting too. But, it's getting better. The main focus is today, and that's all we can do. Love yourself in the making. And don't forget to be human.  #fyp #trans </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@avery.wade.kelley/video/7279150360457907502" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-15T20:21:16+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@avery.wade.kelley/video/7279887328573771051</id>
    <title>Be Human. #fyp </title>
    <updated>2023-09-17T20:01:08+00:00</updated>
    <content>Be Human. #fyp </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@avery.wade.kelley/video/7279887328573771051" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-17T20:01:08+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@avery.wade.kelley/video/7280225171963710762</id>
    <title>#stitch with @Avery Wade Been a while since I've done a voice check. :] #fyp #trans </title>
    <updated>2023-09-18T17:52:09+00:00</updated>
    <content>#stitch with @Avery Wade Been a while since I've done a voice check. :] #fyp #trans </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@avery.wade.kelley/video/7280225171963710762" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-18T17:52:09+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
