<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse</id>
  <title>@jacobtheseahorse | TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-05-31T10:43:38+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://tiktokrss.uselesslesbians.gay/rss/jacobtheseahorse.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://tiktokrss.uselesslesbians.gay/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>Latest TikToks from @jacobtheseahorse</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7231928724923436315</id>
    <title>Replying to @j.j_ghostly there's no guarantees, it really depends on your surgery and recovery as well as how hormones affect you. also don't forget if you have taken testosterone it's important to stop to get pregnant 🏳️‍⚧️ #trans #transman #chestsurgery</title>
    <updated>2023-05-11T14:17:08+00:00</updated>
    <content>Replying to @j.j_ghostly there's no guarantees, it really depends on your surgery and recovery as well as how hormones affect you. also don't forget if you have taken testosterone it's important to stop to get pregnant 🏳️‍⚧️ #trans #transman #chestsurgery #lactation #lactationconsultant #midwife #healthvisitor #lgbt #pregnancy #humanmilk </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7231928724923436315" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-05-11T14:17:08+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7231940496317287707</id>
    <title>Replying to @emenopi i should be clear that this is my experience but other trans folks have different things that trigger dysphoria and it can be unexpected what will impact you.  I also think I would have had a different response if I'd have been pregna</title>
    <updated>2023-05-11T15:02:49+00:00</updated>
    <content>Replying to @emenopi i should be clear that this is my experience but other trans folks have different things that trigger dysphoria and it can be unexpected what will impact you.  I also think I would have had a different response if I'd have been pregnant before ever taking testosterone as I stayed looked pretty masculine throughout #trans #transpregnancy #pregnancy #dysphoria </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7231940496317287707" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-05-11T15:02:49+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7232289367799205147</id>
    <title>Replying to @kismetkat22 when looking at maternity, of course it's language that has previously only been for women, but saying that trans inclusion only ever impacts language for women is untrue (for example when we talk about healthcare for anyone with </title>
    <updated>2023-05-12T13:36:38+00:00</updated>
    <content>Replying to @kismetkat22 when looking at maternity, of course it's language that has previously only been for women, but saying that trans inclusion only ever impacts language for women is untrue (for example when we talk about healthcare for anyone with a prostate). but focusing only on women is part of a wider tactic that paints trans people as powerful monsters and women as victims.  please know I'm not accusing you (commentor) with this, but your questions are phrased in a way that suggests you've been exposed to this narrative. when trans people are included it destabilises the power of cis men who want to keep us down so they are seeking to divide us and make us fear each other, instead of the true people with power. #trans #feminism #lgbt #feminism #feminist #intersectionalfeminism #transgender #queertok #queer #ally #translivesmatter #transwomenarewomen </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7232289367799205147" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-05-12T13:36:38+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7232313269246119194</id>
    <title>#stitch with @Sam 🏳️‍🌈  for context - my grandparents raised me so coming out to them was a big deal! my grandfather was quite lecherous to women (and to me pre-transition 🙃) which is why I suspect he was bi, but perhaps that was a misogenistic performanc</title>
    <updated>2023-05-12T15:09:23+00:00</updated>
    <content>#stitch with @Sam 🏳️‍🌈  for context - my grandparents raised me so coming out to them was a big deal! my grandfather was quite lecherous to women (and to me pre-transition 🙃) which is why I suspect he was bi, but perhaps that was a misogenistic performance. who knows 🤷🏻‍♂️ #gay #lgbt #queer #family #bisexual #pansexual #comingout #90s #grandparents #trauma</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7232313269246119194" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-05-12T15:09:23+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7233348684337941786</id>
    <title>There are days that I can't do things, days that I can and days that I pay the price for trying. I have breathing pattern disorder from having Covid and because that hasn't been treated I can't access the Long Covid Physio that I've waited so long for. th</title>
    <updated>2023-05-15T10:07:21+00:00</updated>
    <content>There are days that I can't do things, days that I can and days that I pay the price for trying. I have breathing pattern disorder from having Covid and because that hasn't been treated I can't access the Long Covid Physio that I've waited so long for. this is a vulnerable moment for me but I know I'm not alone in having a hidden disability and how impactful it is. please be kind #longcovid #covid #migraines #breathing #airhunger #fatigue #brainfog #physio #physiotherapy #emotional #hiddendisabilities #adhd #audhd #capcut #lgbt #transgender </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7233348684337941786" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-05-15T10:07:21+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7233413194168012059</id>
    <title>Replying to @kinj.apan I could only make drops at a time because chest surgery removed a significant amount of my breast tissue, but it's still a miracle that it could happen at all! many trans guys feed from their bodies in one way or another, often usin</title>
    <updated>2023-05-15T14:17:38+00:00</updated>
    <content>Replying to @kinj.apan I could only make drops at a time because chest surgery removed a significant amount of my breast tissue, but it's still a miracle that it could happen at all! many trans guys feed from their bodies in one way or another, often using an SNS system or similar to supplement what they make with their body. #trans #infantfeeding #chestfeeding #breastfeeding #lgbt #transgender #humanmilk #lactation #chestsurgery </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7233413194168012059" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-05-15T14:17:38+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7233487862279277851</id>
    <title>a really lovely OT reached out to me to offer support on a tiktok earlier and my first response was a trauma response because of this experience. one of many instances of medical trauma that I've experienced over the years. sorry to be a Debby Downer but </title>
    <updated>2023-05-15T19:07:24+00:00</updated>
    <content>a really lovely OT reached out to me to offer support on a tiktok earlier and my first response was a trauma response because of this experience. one of many instances of medical trauma that I've experienced over the years. sorry to be a Debby Downer but my guess is I'm not the only one on here who has these kinds of experiences. the intersection of ADHD, autism, menstrual health and mental health all coincidence here and with distanced hindsight of nearly 20 years I can see how vulnerable my young self was. they deserved better. #ot #medical #medicaltrauma #lgbt #period #pmdd #depression #mentalhealth #pms </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7233487862279277851" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-05-15T19:07:24+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7236027075994438938</id>
    <title>Replying to @user9152714924757 it would be unfair to all the women who don't experience pregnancy as a feminine experience to claim that is *has* to be that or you're doing it wrong. that kind of thinking harms more women than it does trans people. (and i</title>
    <updated>2023-05-22T15:21:03+00:00</updated>
    <content>Replying to @user9152714924757 it would be unfair to all the women who don't experience pregnancy as a feminine experience to claim that is *has* to be that or you're doing it wrong. that kind of thinking harms more women than it does trans people. (and it's not a surprise that the far right that push these anti-trans agendas are also anti-women and anti-choice) #trans #pregnancy #feminine #masculine #gender #ally #queer #autonomy #mybodymychoice </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7236027075994438938" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-05-22T15:21:03+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7239288115121229083</id>
    <title>Replying to @sarasaur89 you're right I guess? but probably not in the way you think you are. #trans #autonomy #freedom #choice #gender #joy #lgbt #pride </title>
    <updated>2023-05-31T10:15:29+00:00</updated>
    <content>Replying to @sarasaur89 you're right I guess? but probably not in the way you think you are. #trans #autonomy #freedom #choice #gender #joy #lgbt #pride </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7239288115121229083" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-05-31T10:15:29+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7239295404192451866</id>
    <title>my next hyperfocus was designing t-shirts so expect to hear about that soon 👀 but seriously... how do I get this focus back to make a  flower picture for my MIL?! ahhhh! #adhd #audhd #actuallyautistic #hyperfocus #timeblindness </title>
    <updated>2023-05-31T10:43:38+00:00</updated>
    <content>my next hyperfocus was designing t-shirts so expect to hear about that soon 👀 but seriously... how do I get this focus back to make a  flower picture for my MIL?! ahhhh! #adhd #audhd #actuallyautistic #hyperfocus #timeblindness </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7239295404192451866" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-05-31T10:43:38+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
