<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse</id>
  <title>@jacobtheseahorse | TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-07-28T20:58:33+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://tiktokrss.uselesslesbians.gay/rss/jacobtheseahorse.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://tiktokrss.uselesslesbians.gay/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>Latest TikToks from @jacobtheseahorse</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7255608671252548891</id>
    <title>Replying to @saibuh being pregnant is hard, being trans (in our society) is hard. being trans and pregnant brings extra layers of difficulty. by making perinatal services more trans inclusive we can make hundreds and hundreds of people's lives better ever</title>
    <updated>2023-07-14T09:47:22+00:00</updated>
    <content>Replying to @saibuh being pregnant is hard, being trans (in our society) is hard. being trans and pregnant brings extra layers of difficulty. by making perinatal services more trans inclusive we can make hundreds and hundreds of people's lives better every year, for the thousands that come after us.  you can find out more about what I do in my (link) in (bio).  #trans #midwife #pregnancy #pregnant #obstetrics #inclusion #diversity #transgender #perinatalmentalhealth </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7255608671252548891" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-14T09:47:22+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7255614584747330842</id>
    <title>Replying to @30yearoldlady when trans people get together irl the thing we talk about the least is gender. there's no struggle or expectations, we just exist as humans, trusting that the person in front of us knows best who they are. gender is at its most</title>
    <updated>2023-07-14T10:10:20+00:00</updated>
    <content>Replying to @30yearoldlady when trans people get together irl the thing we talk about the least is gender. there's no struggle or expectations, we just exist as humans, trusting that the person in front of us knows best who they are. gender is at its most boring when it's cisnormative, rigid and imposed.  #trans #transgender #gender </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7255614584747330842" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-14T10:10:20+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7255740784996044059</id>
    <title>nonbinaries of all grump levels welcome 💛🤍💜🖤 also just a reminder that nonbinary people can use any pronouns (including "gendered" ones and can look any way that feels right to them. #nonbinaryday #enby #nonbinary #trans</title>
    <updated>2023-07-14T18:20:05+00:00</updated>
    <content>nonbinaries of all grump levels welcome 💛🤍💜🖤 also just a reminder that nonbinary people can use any pronouns (including "gendered" ones and can look any way that feels right to them. #nonbinaryday #enby #nonbinary #trans</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7255740784996044059" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-14T18:20:05+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7255947776498945307</id>
    <title>at 11 years old I couldn't see a world with me in it. it sometimes feels miraculous that I'm still here at all.  it feels incredible to conceive that I have the chance to live until I see that older man in the mirror.  when we say "protect trans youth", w</title>
    <updated>2023-07-15T07:43:26+00:00</updated>
    <content>at 11 years old I couldn't see a world with me in it. it sometimes feels miraculous that I'm still here at all.  it feels incredible to conceive that I have the chance to live until I see that older man in the mirror.  when we say "protect trans youth", we're talking from experience as the trans youth that needed protecting.  #trans #oldagefilter #mentalhealth </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7255947776498945307" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-15T07:43:26+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7256320181255867674</id>
    <title>Replying to @ms_nightstar this was a difficult video to record and I imagine it might be a difficult video to watch. please be careful with yourself while watching. being targeted during my pregnancy was an event that triggered a deeply powerful shift in </title>
    <updated>2023-07-16T07:48:33+00:00</updated>
    <content>Replying to @ms_nightstar this was a difficult video to record and I imagine it might be a difficult video to watch. please be careful with yourself while watching. being targeted during my pregnancy was an event that triggered a deeply powerful shift in my mental health that left me very unwell for 2 years and hugely affected my relationship with my baby (and everyone else). I was also let down by mental health services despite reaching out for help, but that's another story  #trans #mentalhealth #SA #survivor #storytime #transgender #pregnancy #tw </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7256320181255867674" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-16T07:48:33+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7259387467789241626</id>
    <title>everyone who cares about trans and nonbinary people and their families is welcome to come! tickets are FREE - pm me for the link  in conjunction with #barnardos and #mygenderation @Fox Fisher  #trans #transpac #transgender #families #parents #transparents</title>
    <updated>2023-07-24T14:11:05+00:00</updated>
    <content>everyone who cares about trans and nonbinary people and their families is welcome to come! tickets are FREE - pm me for the link  in conjunction with #barnardos and #mygenderation @Fox Fisher  #trans #transpac #transgender #families #parents #transparents #manchester </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7259387467789241626" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-24T14:11:05+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7259400449051102490</id>
    <title>Replying to @philipmichaelmont you can't always tell someone is trans and you can't always tell someone is pregnant 🤷🏻‍♂️ training for midwives and other birthworkers coming up in August -  bit . ly / seacourses for tickets source for statistic from CQC 2</title>
    <updated>2023-07-24T15:01:26+00:00</updated>
    <content>Replying to @philipmichaelmont you can't always tell someone is trans and you can't always tell someone is pregnant 🤷🏻‍♂️ training for midwives and other birthworkers coming up in August -  bit . ly / seacourses for tickets source for statistic from CQC 2022. link available at transparentchange•co•uk / resources  #midwifery #midwife #birth #pregnancy #pregnantman #birth #education #lgbt #trans #transgender #cqc </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7259400449051102490" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-24T15:01:26+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7260114696081034523</id>
    <title>#duet with @THOSE GUYS #Duet  starting my medical transition 13 years ago there were so many unknowns and I was terrified that I would lose my ability to sing. it took me a long time to work out how to sing with this new voice and for a long time I was sc</title>
    <updated>2023-07-26T13:13:03+00:00</updated>
    <content>#duet with @THOSE GUYS #Duet  starting my medical transition 13 years ago there were so many unknowns and I was terrified that I would lose my ability to sing. it took me a long time to work out how to sing with this new voice and for a long time I was scared to sing because I couldn't pitch properly. it brings me such joy to see all the voice coaches and things that are available now, it would have made such a difference to me to have access to that! #voice #song #testosteronevoiceupdate #testosterone #transition #adele #lgbt #trans #singing #music #tvoice </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7260114696081034523" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-26T13:13:03+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7260935196084571419</id>
    <title>Replying to @fxshboness I wish I had solid data to give you but it doesn't exist yet.  I took testosterone thinking it would make me infertile and I deeply grieved the loss of my fertility. but I got hope when I saw other trans guys getting pregnant and I</title>
    <updated>2023-07-28T18:17:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Replying to @fxshboness I wish I had solid data to give you but it doesn't exist yet.  I took testosterone thinking it would make me infertile and I deeply grieved the loss of my fertility. but I got hope when I saw other trans guys getting pregnant and I took the leap to pause testosterone and try.  and now I'm a Papa to two littles that I grew in my body. #transpregnancy #trans #transgender #lgbt #babies #testosterone #hormones #fertility #pregnancy #parents </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7260935196084571419" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-28T18:17:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7260976819376082202</id>
    <title>I am a loved person. I am a joyful person. I am have so many wonderful ways to describe myself and trans is one of them. cis and trans are descriptors, they are used to describe whether your sex assigned at birth and your gender align. that's it. there's </title>
    <updated>2023-07-28T20:58:33+00:00</updated>
    <content>I am a loved person. I am a joyful person. I am have so many wonderful ways to describe myself and trans is one of them. cis and trans are descriptors, they are used to describe whether your sex assigned at birth and your gender align. that's it. there's no logical reason to be threatened by them. #cis #trans #joy #describeyourself #lgbt #mii #wii </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@jacobtheseahorse/video/7260976819376082202" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-28T20:58:33+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
