<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@manic.toxicity</id>
  <title>@manic.toxicity | TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-06-10T22:06:46+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://tiktokrss.uselesslesbians.gay/rss/manic.toxicity.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://tiktokrss.uselesslesbians.gay/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>Latest TikToks from @manic.toxicity</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@manic.toxicity/video/7241292452231957803</id>
    <title>mental health matters, in every aspect of the phrase. no matter how much you feel like you, or what youre going through, doesnt matter… it does. it’s important to recognize your self worth and the things you di and dont deserve in life. you dont deserve e</title>
    <updated>2023-06-05T19:53:18+00:00</updated>
    <content>mental health matters, in every aspect of the phrase. no matter how much you feel like you, or what youre going through, doesnt matter… it does. it’s important to recognize your self worth and the things you di and dont deserve in life. you dont deserve every bad thing that happens. i get alot of wuestions about the tattoo ok my collar bone: “no rain, no flowers”. i got that tattoo and associate it with my trauma. good things wont come, until after bad shit does. as much as it sucks going through it, you grow from what you go through. always remmeber to prioritize yourself because its one of the most important things. it can be hard, especialy if you have people pleasing tendencies such as myself, but you have to work through it.  i was clean for five years before my relapse, and it was very hard. remmeber that somrwhere, even if you dont see it, theres always someone who cares about you. if you need to, reach out. reach out to a friend, a loved one, a partner, a coworker, a therapist, anyone that you can get some help from. battling mental illness is such a difficult, long, exhausting journey. as taxing as it feels most of the time, youre making progress and you should always celebrate atleast trying !  i know i dont really use my platform to speak about this alot, honestly ill probably get some rude comments or remarkes, but oh well.  always remember that youre loved and that youre worth living. stay strong, stay gorgeous/handsome, and keep on livin. dont forget to have fun doing it all :)  i love all you nerds &lt;3  (yes i am still sick lmao, im almost completely over it tho!! &lt;3 ) #mentalhealthmatters #fyp #foryou #clean </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@manic.toxicity/video/7241292452231957803" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-05T19:53:18+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@manic.toxicity/video/7242415030208187691</id>
    <title>steal all my lines from this guy names brian ;) #fyp #foryou </title>
    <updated>2023-06-08T20:29:23+00:00</updated>
    <content>steal all my lines from this guy names brian ;) #fyp #foryou </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@manic.toxicity/video/7242415030208187691" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-08T20:29:23+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@manic.toxicity/video/7242416063239949611</id>
    <title>sorry, girl, i hope you understand &lt;3 #fyp #foryou </title>
    <updated>2023-06-08T20:33:21+00:00</updated>
    <content>sorry, girl, i hope you understand &lt;3 #fyp #foryou </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@manic.toxicity/video/7242416063239949611" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-08T20:33:21+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@manic.toxicity/video/7242434926610533678</id>
    <title>yeah yeah i did it again  (i get off work at 10pm CST… can we hit 100k by then..? ✨🤯)  #fyp #foryou </title>
    <updated>2023-06-08T21:46:32+00:00</updated>
    <content>yeah yeah i did it again  (i get off work at 10pm CST… can we hit 100k by then..? ✨🤯)  #fyp #foryou </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@manic.toxicity/video/7242434926610533678" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-08T21:46:32+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@manic.toxicity/video/7242741608565771563</id>
    <title>my mental standpoints have changed alot in the past two months and im not wuite sure if its good or bad. ive blocked out alot of things that hurt me consecutively in attempt to better myself   im doing my best to grow as a person, learn my self worth, bat</title>
    <updated>2023-06-09T17:36:53+00:00</updated>
    <content>my mental standpoints have changed alot in the past two months and im not wuite sure if its good or bad. ive blocked out alot of things that hurt me consecutively in attempt to better myself   im doing my best to grow as a person, learn my self worth, battle my mental illnesses, love myself, and much more.  it took a long time for me to realize that the most important person in my life, is me. if i dont take care of me properly, my life would cease to exist.  i go through alot mentally and physically, that i tend to not share with the internet. ive had a hard childhood, all things considered. ive had a devestating rise into adulthood, but thats not gonna stop me.  im trying to do things that are better for myself and my personal priorities within my own head. i have bad days, and good days. sadly, it all just takes time.  Ive grown much more, in many ways, since i was young. im much healthier than i was just a few years ago. but the mindest ive recently developed, “block every negative thing iut of your life”, may or may not be a good one.  its taken me alot of trial and error, hard work, dedication, breakdowns, tears, sweat, and blood to get to were i am today. though i know ive made progress, its hard to recognize it for yourself sometimes.  i went home to read all the comments on the video i made about me being clean from self harm, and sobbed violently. not in a bad way, but because so many people were proud of me without even knowing my full story. and to attract people like all of you, i am eternally grateful.  i love you all so much, thank you for all your support.  (im much better writing that i am at talking, so please excuse my essay of a caption, lol)  p.s. im sorry for any typos, tiktok wont autocorrect anything and i type very quickly) #fyp #mentalhealthmatters #mentalillness #loveyourself </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@manic.toxicity/video/7242741608565771563" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-09T17:36:53+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@manic.toxicity/video/7242748950300626218</id>
    <title>can i get a kiss? #fyp #foryou </title>
    <updated>2023-06-09T18:05:13+00:00</updated>
    <content>can i get a kiss? #fyp #foryou </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@manic.toxicity/video/7242748950300626218" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-09T18:05:13+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@manic.toxicity/video/7242786552235953454</id>
    <title>i dont wanna dall in love, NOPE #fyp #foryou </title>
    <updated>2023-06-09T20:31:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>i dont wanna dall in love, NOPE #fyp #foryou </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@manic.toxicity/video/7242786552235953454" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-09T20:31:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@manic.toxicity/video/7243178665926774058</id>
    <title>will everybody please give him a little bit of space #fyp #foryou</title>
    <updated>2023-06-10T21:52:41+00:00</updated>
    <content>will everybody please give him a little bit of space #fyp #foryou</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@manic.toxicity/video/7243178665926774058" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-10T21:52:41+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@manic.toxicity/video/7243179494498929962</id>
    <title>you are a, walking, second place medal.  #fyp #foryou  THANK YOU ALL SO MUCH FOR 100K!! I LOVE YOU ALL SO SO MUCH!!! </title>
    <updated>2023-06-10T21:55:57+00:00</updated>
    <content>you are a, walking, second place medal.  #fyp #foryou  THANK YOU ALL SO MUCH FOR 100K!! I LOVE YOU ALL SO SO MUCH!!! </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@manic.toxicity/video/7243179494498929962" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-10T21:55:57+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@manic.toxicity/video/7243182263477882154</id>
    <title>ima grow up and be an astronaut:)) #fyp #foryou </title>
    <updated>2023-06-10T22:06:46+00:00</updated>
    <content>ima grow up and be an astronaut:)) #fyp #foryou </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@manic.toxicity/video/7243182263477882154" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-10T22:06:46+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
